

EKREM CAN DEVE

Computer Engineer

Email

devecann@gmail.com

Telefon

+905368259986

Adres

Ankara/Türkiye

Web Sayfası

devecann.vercel.app

Github

notCan

Skills **HTML** CSS Sass Less Bootstrap **Tailwind JavaScript TypeScript NodeJS VueJS NuxtJS Express NestJS** Dart Flutter Spring Git Github/Gitlab Bitbucket PostgreSQL

MongoDB

Firebase

Docker

Summary

I'm detail-oriented Computer Engineer. I experienced my object oriented programming knowledge by learning Java, C# software languages and developing many projects. I'm currently working for full stack developmen and pixel art. I'm trying to learn about microservices rn.

Experiences

Lanista Software, Van/Turkey, Jr. Frontend Developer

May 2022 - Current

After internship i started as a frontend developer and continued company projects. I learn a lot git based CMSs and API based CMSs. And i work with server side frontend frameworks like nuxt and next. And i learn about microservices for improved backends.

Lanista Software, Van/Turkey, Software Developer Intern

Feb 2022 - May 2022

I started as a full stack developer in here. Afterwards i continued as a frontend developer because i have more experience in this area and i wanted to improve myself frontend development and server side development frameworks.

TR Eğitim ve Teknoloji A.Ş., Ankara/Turkey, Mobile App Developer

Aug 2021 - Sept 2021

Me and my team started a mobile project for a web page. Web page is a LMS. With this project university students can meet experienced peoples and this experienced peoples can creates courses in this system. We used flutter and dart for this project. Also i learn bloc/cubit for state management. And i work with third party api.

TR Eğitim ve Teknoloji A.Ş., Ankara/Turkey, Software Developer Intern

July 2021 - Aug 2021

Me and my team developed a test module for VizyonerGenç. Our motivation in developing this project was that the employer can choose better employees for job. I used nestjs for backend development and we use vuejs for frontend and mongodb. I wrote my codes with the code-first approach.

Education

Computer Engineering

Süleyman Demirel University

2017-2021 2.99/4.00

Math

Prof. Dr. Necati Erşen Anatolian Teacher High School

2013-2017 80,85/100